veri5digital.com 2019-10-27

# Privacy Policy | Veri5Digital

Currently our license to operate as an Authentication User Agency (“AUA”) has been suspended on account of Supreme Court Judgement which suspended license of several AUA’s on the ground of public policy. But in the event that the license is reinstated, we will be able to provide access to many Aadhaar based services including Sub-Authentication User Agency (“Sub-AUA”) services as contemplated by the Unique Identification Authority of India (“UIDAI”). Towards the provision of the above mentioned services in the event of reinstatement of our AUA license, the Veri5Digital Portal may require you to provide certain pieces of information about yourself or your entity. Please read below the Privacy Policy of Veri5Digital that sets out the manner and terms of the treatment of the information if and so collected. The following Privacy Policy will be applicable for other products which we offer such as KYC Aadhaar, KYC Video ID, Hosted Aadhaar AUA/KUA, eSign, eNach, Hosted Aadhaar Vault.

Khosla Labs reserves the right to vary the privacy policy from time to time, such variations becoming effective immediately upon posting of the varied Privacy Policy on [www.veri5digital.com](http://veri5digital.com/)

We will be collecting a host of information including IP Address, geo location, cookies, browser information, device information etc.

The information being collected may pertain to a natural person or a corporation/entity availing the Sub-AUA services.

Khosla Labs is committed to protecting the personal information of customers and strives to maintain the privacy of all personal information that Khosla Labs will have access to.

Personal information refers to any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained. For the purpose of this policy, sensitive personal data or information has been considered as a part of Personal Information.

Together all such information being collected shall be referred to as the Information

### Utilisation of the Information

The Information collected will be used for the following purposes:

  * Verify the identity of the customer (in line with the standards as expected by the UIDAI)
  * Complete the on boarding procedure for a customer of Veri5 Digital
  * Complete transactions effectively and bill for Veri5 Digital Services
  * Respond to requests for service or assistance
  * Perform market analysis, market research, business and operational analysis.
  * Internal assessments, operations and related activities
  * Ensure adherence to legal and regulatory requirements for prevention and detection of frauds and crimes
  * Information collected from cookies and other technologies, like pixel tags, to improve customer experience.

### Accessing and updating customer information

Each customer can access her relevant personal information, or in the case of a corporation/entity, its customer information on record by accessing the client portal.

If the information so linked to your profile is incorrect, the customer is required to update the information at the earliest. This can be done by editing your Profile information or dropping a mail to [support@veri5digital.com](mailto:support@veri5digital.com)

You have the right to request that Our Company erase your personal data if stored by the Company by addressing an email to the grievance officer listed below.

### Disclosure of Information

Internal Use: Khosla Labs and its employees may utilise the Information for the purposes as set out in the ‘Utilisation of the Information’ section.

Authorised Third Parties: Khosla Labs may at its discretion employ, contract or include Third Parties external to itself for strategic, tactical and operational purposes. Such sharing of Information is governed by contractual agreements that are in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. The agreements ensure that the Information can be utilised by the Third Party only in a manner and for purposes that are specifically contemplated by us in the governing agreement.

Government agencies: Khosla Labs may share any and all parts of the Information with Government agencies, administrative bodies, authorised law enforcement agencies, court, regulatory/governmental authority or any other organisation, individual or entity for the following reasons:

  * Verification of identity
  * Prevention, detection, investigation including but not limited to cyber incidents, prosecution and punishment of offences
  * To comply with any applicable law, order, regulation, or government request
  * To enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violation
  * To detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues
  * For any other purpose as required by law, judicial or administrative order or regulation

### Security Practices and Procedures

Khosla Labs adopts reasonable security practices and procedures, in line with international standard IS/ISO/IEC 27001, to include, technical, operational, managerial and physical security controls in order to protect the Information from unauthorised access, or disclosure while it is under control.

Internal access to the Information is on a need- only basis. Further, employees and personnel of Khosla Labs are bound by Code of Conduct and Confidentiality Policies which obligate them to protect the confidentiality of the Information.

Adequate steps are taken to ensure that third parties to whom the Information is shared adopt reasonable level of security practices and procedures to ensure security of the Information

The Information will be retained for as long as is required to provide the services to the customer, or as may be required for internal operations or as may be required by law.

If you have any questions, grievances, requests, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy or relevant terms or conditions you may contact us using the information below:

Ms. Sindhu V. Reddy, General Counsel,

Khosla Labs Private Limited,Second Floor, Above Cafe Coffee Day, GRS Tower, #18/2A, Sarjapur Main Rd, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560103. 

E-mail ID: [sindhu@khoslalabs.com](mailto:sindhu@khoslalabs.com). 

Phone: [080 3959 1448](tel:08039591448)

The aforesaid person shall redress the grievance raised by you within a month’s time perusing the same.
